vbstyles.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy - VBStyles

By using http://www.vbstyles.com/, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use users' information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

We care seriously about protecting your privacy. Please send us any questions and/or comments you may have.

**Summary**

  * We will never spam you or give your personal information to anyone.
  * You can always request to remove your information from our servers and databases.

**What information do we collect?**

**Personal: Name, email addresses, phone number, and password**  
All passwords are stored on our server in encrypted form - even we can not tell what they are! If you lose your password, you request us to send a secret URL to your email address, using which you can reset your password. Your phone number will be used only for verifying the style purchase and won't be used for any other purpose.

 **Usage: Number of logins, last login, activity and error logs**  
This data helps us monitor VBStyles's health, interest and diagnose errors and slowness issues when they crop up. We use your phone number for payment verification only and no other purpose.

**How we treat your information?**

**We will never spam you.**  
**We will never disclose your personal information without your permission.**  
We will never sell, rent or share your personal information with a 3rd party, especially your email addresses and phone numbers, without your express permission, unless required by law. Never ever! 

**We will only access your personal information when:**

  * You specifically request us to do so (e.g. you are having technical difficulties).
  * It is required by law.
  * It is necessary to maintain our system. 

**Public Forums**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online for example on forums, on profile, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Cookies and log files**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Users must enable cookies to use our site. dealscorner.com sends a "cookie" to your computer that contains an identification number that is unique to you and the computer you are using. We use this cookie to provide you with a continuous experience, and for us to record how our service is being used. 

As is done with most web sites, we log each visit to each web page. A log entry can contain information typically found in the "header" of your web browser's request such as the browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, and the date and time of day. We may also log your cookie's identification number and the URL of the last site you visited. This log information is important for security, audit, quality improvement, as well as for monitoring the health of our service. 

**Links**   
From time to time this web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, VBStyles, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the terms of use and privacy statements of each and every web site they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Contacting the Web Site Admin**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please use [contact us](http://www.vbstyles.com/contact) form to contact us.

Last Updated on June 1, 2011.
